// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
    options: [
      "Hyper Text Preprocessor",
      "Hyper Text Markup Language",
      "Hyper Text Multiple Language",
      "Hyper Tool Multi Language"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What does CSS stand for?",
    answer: "Cascading Style Sheet",
    options: [
      "Common Style Sheet",
      "Colorful Style Sheet",
      "Computer Style Sheet",
      "Cascading Style Sheet"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is not a valid tag name?",
    answer: "School",
    options: [
      "School",
      "paragraph",
      "Header",
      "Table"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How do you referece a class attribute in CSS?",
    answer: "Use of .",
    options: [
      "Use of #",
      "Use of -",
      "Use of *",
      "Use of ."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the followings are the two types of list in HTML?",
    answer: "ol and ul",
    options: [
      "ol and li",
      "li and ul",
      "ol and ul",
      " p and h1"
    ]
  },
 {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The correct sequence of HTML tags for starting a webpage is",
    answer: "HTML, Head, Title, Body",
    options: [
      "Head, Title, HTML, body",
      "HTML, Body, Title, Head",
      "HTML,Title, Body,Head",
      "HTML, Head, Title, Body"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following code will increase the font size, centalize the document and change the font color of a text with class name des",
    answer: ".des{ font-size: 20; color: red, text-align:center}",
    options: [
      ".des{ font-size: 20; color: red, center:True}",
      "#des{ font-size: 20; color: red, center:True}",
      ".des{ font-size: 20; color: red, text-align:center}",
      "#des[font-size: 20; color: red, text-align:center]"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "<!DOCTYPE html> does what ?",
    answer: "It tell the browser the version of the HTML",
    options: [
      "It tell the browser the version of the HTML",
      "It adds styles to our website",
      "It is added to make our website popular",
      "It does not do anything"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "CSS statements must end with?",
    answer: "semicolon (;)",
    options: [
      "colon (:)",
      "semicolon (;)",
      "full-stop (.)",
      "Qustion mark (?)"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the Anchor Attribute is used to specify the language of the linked document ?",
    answer: "None of these",
    options: [
      "alang",
      "lang",
      "hreflang",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Which of the following is not part of the <table> tag"  ,
    answer: "tc",
    options: [
      "td",
      "tr",
      "tc",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "	What is the function of the <style> tag",
    answer: " used for internal CSS",
    options: [
      "	Used for add images, videos and audios to our website",
      "used for internal CSS",
      "used for styling",
      "used to add image"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Which of the following is not a valid CSS property",
    answer: "bgcolor",
    options: [
      "text-align",
      "letter-spacing",
      "color",
      "bgcolor"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which extension will you save your CSS project with?",
    answer: ".css",
    options: [
      ".html",
      ".design",
      ".css",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "A webpage displays a picture. What tag was used to display that picture?",
    answer: "img",
    options: [
      "picture",
      "image",
      "img",
      "src"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "How to insert an image in HTML?",
    answer: "<img src = image_location  />",
    options: [
      "using img tag and src attribute",
      "using img tag and url attribute",
      "using img tag and link attribute",
      "using img tag and home attribute"
    ]
  }, {
    numb: 17,
    question: "How do you include interaction in web design?",
    answer: "Use of Javascript",
    options: [
      "Use of HTML",
      "Use of CSS",
      "Use of Javascript",
      "None of the above"
    ]

  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Which of the following tag is used for inserting the largest heading in HTML?",
    answer: "h1",
    options: [
      "h2",
      "h7",
      "h6",
      "h1"
    ]

  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "What is the function of the <br> tag",
    answer: "To move to a new line",
    options: [
      "To add table to our webpage",
      "To move to a new line",
      "To add color and bold our background",
      "None of the above"
    ]

  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Which of the following element is responsible for making the text bold in HTML?",
    answer: "<b>",
    options: [
      "<pre>",
      "<a>",
      "<b>",
      "<br>"
    ]

  },



  ];